MOHAMED ABDELHAMID

20khirala st. Alexandria-Egypt · (+20)1286076217 **Mohamedahmedb133@gmail.com** · <u>Mohamed Abdelhamid | LinkedIn</u>

I am a student in the College of Computer Science, and I am interested in the field of data science, especially the academic field and scientific research, and I seek to develop myself in this field

EXPERIENCE

2021 - NOW

Freelancer, UP WORK

Data analysis freelancer by using (power BI – excel- python)

2020 - 2022

Freelancer, UP WORK

Writing scientific research by using Microsoft office (word-power point-excel)

2020 - 2021

Data Analysis Trainee, HOSPITAL OF PEDIATRIC SURGERIES

EDUCATION

2019-2023

Bachelor of computer science and statistics, ALEXANDRIA UNIVERSITY

CGPA: 3.3 Level: 4

Major: computer science minor: statistics

SKILLS

- communication skills
- project management
- problem solving

- programming with python
- Using R & SPSS

OTHER QUALIFICATION

- English B2
- French A2
- Work with adobe
 XD illustrator
- Good knowledge in
 - C++ & JAVA
 - OOP
 - Data Structure& Algorithm
 - SQL Data base

ACTIVITIES

- Student activities:
 - (8/2021- now) IT- multimedia sector staff member at Enactus Alexandria university
 - (11/2021-3/2022) staff member of media & marketing at career summit project
 - (7/2021-10/2021) staff member of Human resources at evolution project (Affiliated to the Egyptian Syndicate of Scientific Professions)
 - (7/2020-7/2021) staff member at Academic Committee plankton team (Affiliated to the Faculty of Science, Alexandria University)

• certificates:

- Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)
- Data Analysis Challenger track
- Data Analysis professional track
- Python for data science & ML
- Supervised machine learning: regression and classification